lankahost.net 2019-03-05

# Privay Policy

##  Privacy Policy 

**1\. Introduction.**  
LankaHost Web Hosting Network, Sri Lanka respects the privacy of every individual who visits its Web sites and uses its services. This privacy statement provides notice of the standards and terms under which LankaHost Web Hosting Network, Sri Lanka protects the privacy of information supplied by visitors to sites on the World Wide Web that are operated by LankaHost Web Hosting Network, Sri Lanka. This privacy statement provides notice of our information collection practices and of the ways in which your information may be used. This policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically to review this information. 

**2\. Personally Identifiable Information.**  
LankaHost Web Hosting Network, Sri Lanka, typically receives specific data about its Web site visitors only when such information is provided voluntarily, such as when our visitors request information, purchase or enroll for services, provide resume information for employment opportunities, or send us e-mail. Of course, some of these activities require that you give us information, such as when you make a purchase or request certain types of information. 

**We collect the following types of information about you.**

**Contact Information**

  * Name
  * Postal Address
  * City
  * Country
  * Email address
  * Telephone number

Verification Data 

  * Internet Protocol (IP) address for fraud-prevention purposes

Other Information 

LankaHost Web Hosting Network, Sri Lanka will not, however, sell, trade, or otherwise disclose your personally identifiable information unless we are authorized or legally required to do so, or in the case of imminent physical harm to any person. . LankaHost Web Hosting Network, Sri Lanka protects and secures this information by employing commercially customary Web-based security and encryption protocols, an example of which is the Secure Socket Layer (SSL). LankaHost Web Hosting Network, Sri Lanka will treat that portion of the information as non-confidential and non-proprietary and, except as otherwise expressed in this privacy statement, LankaHost Web Hosting Network, Sri Lanka assumes no obligation to protect such information from disclosure. 

**3\. Changes in this Privacy Statement.**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes in this privacy statement, and in other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.
